We hope that your precious time will
continue forever.
I was so excited to come here.
It's too big.
Konomi!
Julia!
Toko!
Maruko!
Aki!
Yori!
Then, let's go to the Tokimeki
exhibition!
Let's have fun!
Please subscribe to my channel.
A bento is here.
This is a Yodonama.
This is a Ioken.
This is fried rice.
This is a Teten.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It's Kiyoken.
Good morning.
We're listening to a new song.
How long should we spoil the song?
I don't know.
We're going to do it today.
Is it okay?
How long should we spoil the song?
Do you remember the new song?
But you can tell us the title of the
song.
Do you remember the song, Dear Friend?
I don't think everyone expected to sing
this new song.
I didn't expect it.
Kanamin is singing.
This is the new costume.
This is the costume for this day.
It's a waste.
Right?
This is the costume like a mermaid.
This is the first time I wear this.
This part is long.
Next, I'll make fried rice.
Do you want fried rice?
Fried rice.
It's good.
This is not only in Yokohama.
We ate it.
Yesterday, a bug came into the dressing
room.
We ate a lunch box.
We closed the lid and left the room
with chopsticks.
We were surprised and left the room
I'm glad that a bug came out of the
dressing room.
It's the season of bugs.
Bye bye.
Bye bye!
Good morning!
Twinkle twinkle twinkle!
Twinkle twinkle!
Oh, it's sparkling!
I'll change my clothes.
I'm in a good mood today.
I was fine when I woke up in the
morning.
I was fine because I thought I was fine
today.
I'm going to put on my makeup.
I still have to wear my hair.
Look at this.
This is my face.
I want to be beautiful.
I'm going to put on my makeup.
We're going to start the rehearsal.
I'll do my best!
I'm a member of CHUHAYA BAND.
I'm the most popular member today.
I'm done!
I still have 5 hours to go.
Do you have 5 hours?
I don't have 5 hours.
I have 5 hours.
I'm done!
8 fried rice left!
Bye bye!
What should I do if I get a punch on my
chest?
I'll just say, ta-da!
The point of this outfit is...
The glitter of this skirt.
It's so shiny.
It shines every time I move.
The glitter represents the sea.
The sunlight in the water moves in a
glittery way.
I think it's good to show that.
Hodowari
I cut my nails.
I'm worried about my small nails.
I want to grow them out.
I'm going to perform.
I'm looking forward to it.
The scenery has changed a lot.
It's totally different from the
previous one.
I like this.
It's like an arena.
It's different from the usual one.
It might be old, but it's close to my
heart.
I love it.
Good morning.
Today is the day before the
competition.
I'm wearing a skirt for the first time.
The competition is about to start.
Let's go.
Wow.
Oh, no.
I'm going to win.
Wow.
This is the one that I pass by.
Oh, no.
I have to pass this.
Wait.
Wow.
I'm going to show you how the stage
looks like.
I'll show you where I can go.
I'm getting goose bumps.
I'm going to cry.
Wow.
I'm getting goose bumps.
I'm going to cry.
What's this?
It's cute.
It's big.
Thank you.
Wow.
It's cute.
It's big.
It's like a monitor.
Look at that.
I'm going to go down the stairs.
Watch out for the stairs.
This is amazing.
It's amazing.
Please subscribe to this channel.
The stage is spacious.
It's spaceful.
He picked up my size.
Oh!
Wow!
The stage is huge and the seats are...
The stage is amazing.
It's different from usual.
I feel like I'm in a festival.
It's so loud.
Ah...
It's big and it's been here for years.
Each one is big.
I want to eat the usual one.
This way.
Thank you for watching.
This live show will really touch the
hair of many of our staff.
It's like we meet ourselves amidst so
many muscular dudes' bodies.
It feels like we're at a festival, or
we're a guest at someone else's show.
You're right.
If this were an extraordinary feeling,
It's totally different from the one in
Arirang.
I can't understand the song if I listen
to it with this kind of bass.
I think I'm going to cry.
They are going to the stage.
Wow, the stage.
Wow, Ayaka, you are stretching.
Please watch it.
There is a passage!
It was my dream to walk through here.
Many idols have passed through here.
I thought it was good.
Did you pass through?
Yes, I did.
Thank you for your viewing.
I can't reach it.
It's quite high.
It's over there.
From above?
Over there?
Then, please go through here.
Be careful because it's low.
Is it B or A on the left side?
It's B.
It's high.
It's also out.
I'll be careful.
It's close.
Thank you for watching.
I don't know how many people will come.
I'm looking forward to it.
I want to throw this to everyone at the
end.
It's a present.
I'll throw it.
I want to appear from there someday.
I'll appear from the audience someday.
It's amazing.
I support it with this weight.
It's amazing to make this stage.
It's a gym.
There is nothing.
Floor, floor, gym floor.
It's like a gym in my school.
Let's do our best.
There's nothing special about the
venue.
We're standing on this stage.
Amazing.
It's a job.
I'm sorry.
It's hard to do it with a case.
It's amazing.
It's quite heavy.
It's small.
NS-san
The screen is so big this time.
Yes, it is.
There are also four-sided screens.
I'm sorry that the screen is so big.
It's a little bit big.
I'm laughing.
Oh, here they are.
They are coming.
Thank you.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
Stage.
How do you feel?
I feel good.
She is so energetic.
3,2,1,4,5,6
We are RAP UNIT.
We are going to show you our
performance.
Thank you for your support.
Please subscribe to our channel.
I'll go to the room beside the row
seats.
Yu cuts her hand!
I can't stop laughing.
I'll continue to push once more with
all my might.
Please be near my side.
Kiss, Kiss, Kiss
So that you can be yourself
I love you
I'mcous-Dancer
Rain flower
Keeper of the bun
Rice Cake
Baking Smash
Why is it that when it rains,
I always seem to be the one crying?
I'll wash away my dirty thoughts
If I don't, I won't be able to walk
Look, let's go wherever we want
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
It's as if my heart is a sunny pattern
I play the sound of a puddle
I play the rainbow piano
Why is it that when I smile,
the world seems to be shining?
I can turn my umbrella around and be
happy
If I don't, I won't be able to walk
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I'll get my body wet somewhere again
I wonder if it's not cold
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I want to share my feelings with them
The scenery that I still don't know is
in front of me
Look, let's go wherever we want
Goodbye, goodbye
Thank you for yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
On the canvas of my damaged heart
I'll draw a fragment of the future
And guide me
Now I can say the reason for my tears
When I'm lost, I remember right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day
I'll ring the rainbow bell
And play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day
I'll wipe away my tears
And wear a rainbow dress